{"mediumQuestions":[{"questionText":"Technology","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"מדע","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מחשבים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"תוכנה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"טכנולוגיה","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Environment","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"אקולוגיה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"טבע","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"סביבה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"חידושים","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Science","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"גרפיקה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ביולוגיה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מדע","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"פיזיקה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Globalization","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"עולם","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"תרבות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"גלובליזציה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"כלכלה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Artificial Intelligence","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"אלגוריתם","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"בינה מלאכותית","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"מתמקד בנתונים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"טכנולוגיה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Economy","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"כלכלה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"פיננסים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"שוק ההון","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מיסים","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Politics","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"ממשלה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"דמוקרטיה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"שלטון","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"פוליטיקה","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Medicine","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"ברחוב","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"בית חולים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"רפואה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"חולצה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Space","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"כוכבים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"כדור הארץ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"חלל","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"גלקסיה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Philosophy","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"חשיבה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"פילוסופיה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"אידיאולוגיה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"תחושות","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"History","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"זמן","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ארכיאולוגיה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"היסטוריה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"ספרים","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Culture","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"אמנות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"תרבות","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"פולקלור","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"תקשורת","isCorrect":false}]}]}